## Barbara Eszter Böszöri

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Reporting KPI-s

Automatize Excel reports

Monitoring SLA-s

Telecommunication

O365 support

**ITSKILLS** 

MS EXCEL ACCESS

MS Word, PowerPoint, Project, SharePoint

Windows, Linux

VBA, Python, SQL

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English-C1/active

German-B1/active

PERSONAL SKILLS

Analytical

Quick learner

Creative

Team player

PERSONAL DETAILS

Address: 15. Miklós str. BP, 1033

Email: eboszori@gmail.com

M:+36709454092

DoB: 20/09/1985

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Self-motivated reporting analyst who is highly efficient and has a good eye of detail. Has extensive experience of monitoring KPIs, design, analyze, and automate Excel reports. And has technical, and customer service skills. Able to come up with creative solutions. A quick learner who can absorb new ideas and can communicate clearly and effectively.

**WORK EXPERIENCE** 

Vodafone Hungary Zrt.

SERVICE QUALITY REPORTING ANALYST January 2012 - Present

*Main activities*: Reporting Key Performance Indicators in support of management and customer requests. Monitoring and analyzing network data, and cooperating with network engineers on proactively detecting and preventing failures.

TECHNICAL SUPPORT TEAM SPECIALIST January 2011 – January 2012

*Main activities*: Investigating technical complaints, and sending them on competent teams, answering technical questions of colleagues. Testing new services and mobile phones.

TECHNICAL ASSISTANT TEAM REPRESENTATIVE April 2010- January 2011

Main activities. Answering technical questions of customers.

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE Augustus 2009-April 2010

Budapest Chamber of Commerce and Industry, Department of International Affairs

INTERN May-October 2008

 $\textit{Main activities.} \ \text{Making presentations, translating, and administrative work.}$ 

**EDUCATION** 

University of Óbuda, Faculty of Information Techniques 2012-

INFORMATION ENGINEERING - Evening course, My next two semesters will be passive

University of West-Hungary, Faculty of Economics, Sopron 2004-2009

ECONOMICS - Pending degree, only the final exam missing

Eötvös József Secondary School, Tiszaújváros 1998-2004

Online courses on Coursera.org, edX.org, in the field of my academic studies